Mohammed Qutubuddin Zafar

Full Stack Developer (3Years +)

Mobile No:

+918686842949

Email:

mail@zafardev.com

Education

B.tech (2016-2019)

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological

University Hyderabad

Diploma (2013-2016)

State Board Of Technical Education & Training Telangana

SSC (2013)

State Board Of Telangana

About Me

I've been a working as a software developer for more than 2 years. I've mostly worked on Typescript, React.js, React Native, Node.js, API Integration(REST, GRAPHQL), Flask, Mongodb, Postgresql, Mysql.

I'd like to work as a Full Stack Developer in product based Companies or where can get Product Ownership



Previous Work Experience

Software Engineer

DawateislamiIndia (Mumbai) 2022 - Present

Software Developer

Calico Infosystem (Hyderabad)

2021 - 2022

Software Developer

MountBlue Technologies (Bangalore) 2019 - 2020

Internships

Software Developer

Own Company

(Jul 2020 - Sep 2020)

Backend Developer

InfowareIndia (Oct 2020 - Dec 2020)

Recent Projects

I h've worked on many projects some of my recent projects are listed Below:

MadaniERP

Erp Software for internal departments of a company. it is on Frappe Python's Framework. Presently working on Hr Module.

DawateislamiIndia

website for Collecting and Managing donations with high security and unique single Payment Qr code. Mostly worked on cloudflare Workers.

FinbookLite

Internal App for Calico infosystem pvt, Itd (Flnance Related App)
In that i worked as a Front End Developer There i Used mostly Algorithms and Data
Structure methods for their Business Logic.

FinScan

Internal app for calico infosystem

App that scans the barcode and get product details from that barcode. after that it is added into cart and user can checkout easily.

Skills

Typescript React Figma Docker

Node

Express

Frappe

ERPNext

Postgresql

MariaDB

MongoDB

Mysql Sqlite

Python

Flask

HTML

CSS

Javascript

React-Native

React-Ionic

GraphQl

TailwindCSS aws amplify

